Stitch was Experiment 626...meet the other 625!
Stitch! The Movie is a comedy, family, animation film directed by Bobs Gannaway.
The continuing adventures of Lilo, a little Hawaiian girl, and
Stitch, the galaxy's most-wanted extraterrestrial.
Stitch, Pleakley, and Dr.
Jumba are all part of the household now, but what
Lilo and Stitch don't know is that Dr.
Jumba brought his other alien "experiments" to Hawaiʻi as well.
Lilo (voice), played by Daveigh Chase.
Stitch (voice), played by Chris Sanders.
Nani (voice), played by Tia Carrere.
Dr. Jumba Jookiba (voice), played by David Ogden Stiers.
Pleakley (voice), played by Kevin McDonald.
Myrtle Edmonds (voice), played by Liliana Mumy.
The Movie is a 2003 American direct-to-video animated science fiction comedy film produced by Walt
Disney Television Animation and Rough Draft Korea, released on August 26, 2003.
It is produced by Tony Craig, Jess Winfield, and Bobs Gannaway; Gannaway also
co-wrote and co-directed with Winfield and Craig, respectively.
It is the second film released in the Lilo & Stitch franchise and the third film chronologically, taking place after the
2002 first film and (by later extension) the 2005 direct-to-video sequel Lilo & Stitch 2: Stitch Has a Glitch.
The film also serves as the backdoor pilot of the spin-off sequel series Lilo & Stitch: The Series,
which Craig, Winfield and Gannaway executive produced and debuted the following month.
The story is an introduction to Jumba Jookiba's other experiments (made
prior to Stitch) that he created via the financing of Dr.
Jacques von Hämsterviel.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.